An assassin on the loose. A president in danger.
Only one man stands between them…
In the Line of Fire is a action, drama, thriller
film directed by Wolfgang Petersen.
Veteran Secret Service agent Frank Horrigan is a man haunted by his failure to
save President Kennedy while serving protection detail in Dallas.
Thirty years later, a man calling himself "Booth" threatens the life of the current President,
forcing Horrigan to come back to protection detail to confront the ghosts from his past.
Frank Horrigan, played by Clint Eastwood.
Mitch Leary, played by John Malkovich.
Lilly Raines, played by Rene Russo.
Al D'Andrea, played by Dylan McDermott.
Bill Watts, played by Gary Cole.
Harry Sargent, played by Fred Thompson.
In the Line of Fire is a 1993 American political action thriller film directed by
Wolfgang Petersen and starring Clint Eastwood, John Malkovich and Rene Russo.
Written by Jeff Maguire, the film is about a disillusioned and obsessed former CIA agent who plans to
assassinate the President of the United States and the Secret Service agent who is tracking him.
Eastwood's character is the sole remaining active-duty Secret
Service agent from the detail that was guarding John F.
Kennedy in Dallas, Texas at the time of his assassination in 1963.
The film also stars Dylan McDermott, Gary Cole, John
Mahoney, and Fred Dalton Thompson.
In the Line of Fire was co-produced by Columbia Pictures and Castle
Rock Entertainment, with Columbia handling distribution.
The film was a critical and commercial success.
It grossed $187 million against a $40 million production budget and
earned three nominations at the 66th Academy Awards.
The film explores themes of assassin, central intelligence agency
(cia), usa president, the white house, bodyguard.
The tone is mind_bending and emotional and intense.